<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<channel>
	<title>Canal personal</title>
	<item>
		<title>Elephants Dream</title>
		<link>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TLkA0RELQ1g</link>
		<description>The first Blender Open Movie from 2006</description>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Elephants%20dream-poster.jpg"/>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Elephants%20dream-fanart.jpg"/>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Big Buck Bunny</title>
		<link>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YE7VzlLtp-4</link>
		<description>Big Buck Bunny tells the story of a giant rabbit with a heart bigger than himself. When one sunny day three rodents rudely harass him, something snaps... and the rabbit ain't no bunny anymore! In the typical cartoon tradition he prepares the nasty rodents a comical revenge.

Licensed under the Creative Commons Attribution license

http://www.bigbuckbunny.org/</description>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Big%20buck%20bunny-poster.jpg"/>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Big%20buck%20bunny-fanart.jpg"/>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Sintel</title>
		<link>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eRsGyueVLvQ</link>
		<description>"Sintel" is an independently produced short film, initiated by the Blender Foundation as a means to further improve and validate the free/open source 3D creation suite Blender. With initial funding provided by 1000s of donations via the internet community, it has again proven to be a viable development model for both open 3D technology as for independent animation film.
This 15 minute film has been realized in the studio of the Amsterdam Blender Institute, by an international team of artists and developers. In addition to that, several crucial technical and creative targets have been realized online, by developers and artists and teams all over the world. www.sintel.org</description>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Sintel-poster.jpg"/>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Sintel-fanart.jpg"/>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Tears of Steel</title>
		<link>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R6MlUcmOul8</link>
		<description>"Tears of Steel" was realized with crowd-funding by users of the open source 3D creation tool Blender. Target was to improve and test a complete open and free pipeline for visual effects in film - and to make a compelling sci-fi film in Amsterdam, the Netherlands.

The film itself, and all raw material used for making it, have been released under the Creatieve Commons 3.0 Attribution license. Visit the tearsofsteel.org website to find out more about this, or to purchase the 4-DVD box with a lot of extras.

(CC) Blender Foundation - http://www.tearsofsteel.org

Duration: 12 minutes. Available also in HD and DCP 2.35:1, Dolby 5.1.

Age: Suitable for 12 years and older. 
Language: English spoken
Production: Blender Institute

Producer: Ton Roosendaal
Director & Writer: Ian Hubert
Director of Photography: Joris Kerbosch
Composer: Joram Letwory

Starring: Derek de Lint, Sergio Hasselbaink, Rogier Schippers, Vanja Rukavina, Denise Rebergen, Jody Bhe, Chris Haley

Crew: Andreas Goralczyk, David Revoy, Francesco Siddi, Jeremy Davidson, Kjartan Tysdal, Nicolo Zubbini, Rob Tuytel, Roman Volodin, Sebastian Koenig, Brecht van Lommel, Campbell Barton, Sergey Sharybin.

Project funding: Blender Foundation, 
Netherlands Film Fund, Cinegrid Amsterdam

Premium Sponsor: Google
Main Sponsors: NVIDIA, Hewlett-Packard Workstations, Camalot AV Services, BlenderGuru.

https://www.facebook.com/mango.open.movie (Facebbok page)
https://plus.google.com/112059823531133148949/ (Google+ page)</description>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Tears%20of%20steel-poster.jpg"/>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Tears%20of%20steel-fanart.jpg"/>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Born of hope</title>
		<link>http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qINwCRM8acM</link>
		<description>Born of Hope is an independent feature film inspired by the Lord of the Rings and produced by Actors at Work Productions in the UK. 
http://www.bornofhope.com

Thanks to Chris Bouchard and the H4G team for putting the film here. For more films by the makers of this and BoH extras please visit.
ActorsatWork
http://www.youtube.com/actorsatwork

Check them out for more videos regarding the film including the audio commentary. 
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elt_l8zisik

A scattered people, the descendants of storied sea kings of the ancient West, struggle to survive in a lonely wilderness as a dark force relentlessly bends its will toward their destruction. Yet amidst these valiant, desperate people, hope remains. A royal house endures unbroken from father to son.

This 70 minute original drama is set in the time before the War of the Ring and tells the story of the Dúnedain, the Rangers of the North, before the return of the King. Inspired by only a couple of paragraphs written by Tolkien in the appendices of the Lord of the Rings we follow Arathorn and Gilraen, the parents of Aragorn, from their first meeting through a turbulent time in their people's history.</description>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Born%20of%20hope-poster.jpg"/>
		<media:thumbnail url="http://pelisalacarta.mimediacenter.info/personalchannel/Born%20of%20hope-fanart.jpg"/>
	</item>
</channel>